// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let Maths = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The decimal form of [Math Processing Error] is",
    answer: "(c) non-terminating non-repeating",
    options: [
      "(a) terminating",
      "(b) non-termining",
      "(c) non-terminating non-repeating",
      "(d) non-terminating non-repeating"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "HCF of 8, 9, 25 is",
    answer:  "(c) 25",
    options: [
      "(a) 8",
      "(b) 9",
      "(c) 25",
      "(d) 1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Which of the following is not irrational?",
    answer:  "(c) (√2 -√3)(√2 + √3)",
    options: [
      "(a) (2 – √3)2",
      "(b) (√2 + √3)2",
      "(c) (√2 -√3)(√2 + √3)",
      "(d)[Math Processing Error]"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The product of a rational and irrational number is",
    answer:"(b) irrational",
    options: [
      "(a) rational",
      "(b) irrational",
      "(c) both of above",
      "(d) none of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The sum of a rational and irrational number is",
    answer:   "A. eXtensible Markup Language", 
    options: [
      "(a) rational",
      "(b) irrational",
      "(c) both of above",
      "(d) none of above"
    ]
  },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question:"The product of two different irrational numbers is always",
      answer: "(b) irrational",
      options:[
        "(a) rational",
        "(b) irrational",
        "(c) both of above",
        "(d) none of above"
      ]
  },
 {
     numb: 7,
     question: "The sum of two irrational numbers is always",
     answer: "(a) irrational",
      options:[
        "(a) irrational",
        "(b) rational",
        "(c) rational or irrational",
        "(d) one"
      ]
 },
 {
     numb: 8,
     question: "If b = 3, then any integer can be expressed as a =",
     answer:  "(a) 3q, 3q+ 1, 3q + 2",
     options:[
         "(a) 3q, 3q+ 1, 3q + 2",
         "(b) 3q",
         "(c) none of the above",
         "(d) 3q+ 1"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 9,
     question: "The product of three consecutive positive integers is divisible by",
     answer:  "(b) 6",
     options:[
         "(a) 4",
         "(b) 6",
         "(c) no common factor",
         "(d) only 1"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 10,
     question: "10. The set A = {0,1, 2, 3, 4, …} represents the set of",
     answer:  "(a) whole numbers",
     options:[
         "(a) whole numbers",
         "(b) integers",
         "(c) natural numbers",
         "(d) even numbers"

     ]
 }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];